[
	{
		"question" : "_______ is the first female prime minister of England.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "Patricia Rawlings" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "Glenys Kimmmock" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "Margaret Thatcher" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "Angela Billingham" }
		],
		"correct" : 2
	},

	{
		"question" : "There are _______ continents in the world .",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "Eleven" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "Seven" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "Ten" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "Eight" }
		],
		"correct" : 1
	},

	{
		"question" : "Twitter was launched in what year _______ .",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "2003" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "2006" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "2004" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "2005" }
		],
		"correct" : 1
	},

	{
		"question" : "_______  is the most visited tourist attraction in the world.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "Eiffel Tower" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "Nigara Falls" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "Roman Coliseum" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "Las Vegas Strip" }
		],
		"correct" : 3
	},

	{
		"question" : "_______  is the first person to win two Nobel Laureate prizes.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "Marie Curie" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "Linus Pauling" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "Frederick Sanger" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "John Bardeen" }
		],
		"correct" : 0
	},

	{
		"question" : "The city  of _______ hosted the 1988 Olympic Games.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "Seoul" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "Berlin" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "Barcelona" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "Los Angeles" }
		],
		"correct" : 0
	},

	{
		"question" : "_______ is not a programming language.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "Cobra" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "Ada" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "Kotlin" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "Shery" }
		],
		"correct" : 3,
		"feedback" : "Did you know Cobra is a programming language? oh now you do"
	},

	{
		"question" : "The s in https stands for _______ .",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "service" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "secure" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "severe" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "serious" }
		],
		"correct" : 1
	},


	{
		"question" : "Real Madrid FC has won the UCL _______ times.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "11" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "10" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "12" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "13" }
		],
		"correct" : 2
	},


	{
		"question" : "The speed of sound is _______.",
		"answer" : [
			{ "id" : 0, "text" : "340.29m/s" },
			{ "id" : 1, "text" : "242.29m/s" },
			{ "id" : 2, "text" : "330.29m/s" },
			{ "id" : 3, "text" : "574.92m/s" }
		],
		"correct" : 0
	}
]